hasoffers.com 2014-12-31

# HasOffers Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the HasOffers™ website located at www.hasoffers.com (the “Site”) – property of HasOffers, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“HasOffers,” “we” or “us”). HasOffers is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors’ personally identifiable information. We provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) in order to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by us on our site www.hasoffers.com and through our HasOffers platform. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged HasOffers. You must agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, including our use of cookies in order to: a) access or use our Site; and/or (b) subscribe to any of the HasOffers affiliate network management products and/or services (the “Services”) offered on the Site (each, a “Subscription”). Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies on the Site shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future attempts to access the Site and/or any Subscription of the Services. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to become a subscriber (“Subscriber”) to the Services and/or use the Site in any manner or form whatsoever. HasOffers has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy and Children’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) and [TRUSTed Cloud Program Requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/TRUSTed-cloud/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does only covers information collected through our site [www.hasoffers.com](http://www.hasoffers.com/) and our Hasoffers Platform. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@hasoffers.com](mailto:support@hasoffers.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). 

## Privacy Policies Used in Connection with Your Subscription.

Potential affiliates that sign up for the affiliate program that you establish by and through the Services do so from links on your website or via a Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) supplied to you via the Services (collectively, “Subscription Website”). Such affiliates’ information is stored on the password-protected portal established by and through the Services. HasOffers will not access the affiliate information stored on your password-protected portal unless you specifically request that we do so. You are solely responsible for choosing, and uploading to applicable areas of your Subscription Website, a privacy policy to govern your affiliate program, in which conspicuous written notice is given to internet users who access your Subscription Website (“Subscription Users”) that cookies may be used to collect anonymous traffic data, and for which you receive consent prior to placing cookies on the internet device of any such Subscription User. HasOffers is in no way responsible for the collection, storage, use and/or distribution of any data that is submitted by and through your Subscription Website. 

## Personally Identifiable Information.

We collect personally identifiable information on the Site when you attempt to become a Subscriber or otherwise choose to provide personally identifiable information to us. Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This may include, but is not limited to: name, business entity name and/or your title with the applicable business entity, as well as your personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or cellular telephone numbers, fax number, credit card and/or any other information requested on the applicable Subscriber registration form. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, your credit card shall be considered “Sensitive Information.” If you apply for a job on our site we will collect your name, email address , phone number and resume. We use this information to contact you regarding the position in which you had applied and to determine if you are a good candidate for the position. If you wish to share a job post with your friend, we will collect their name and email address. We use this information to send them a one-time email inviting them to view the invite. We do not store this information for any reason. 

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the Site’s pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows ’98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage. **Social Media (Features) and Widgets** Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. **Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider** You can log in to our support section of the site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons.

To enhance your experience with the Site, we use “cookies.” You cannot use this site or the Services without agreeing to accept the cookies that we use with the Site. For more specific information on the cookies we use, please see Exhibit A, below. Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. Cookies are used by your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. You may set your browser to warn you that cookies are in use, or to block the use of cookies. Most browsers are set to accept cookies. If your browser is not set to accept cookies, certain uses of the Site may require you to go to your browser user preferences to enable cookies. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you change computers, operating systems or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. The use of third party cookies is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. We or our third party tracking utility partner may additionally collect information using Web beacons, which are commonly referred to in the industry as web bugs, pixel tags or Clear GIFs. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on the Site, in our Services, or in our emails to deliver cookies, count visits and determine if an email has been opened and acted upon. HasOffers also utilizes a third party retargeting campaign that uses cookies to keep track of your interaction with HasOffers. You may opt-out of such retargeting by clicking here <https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy> and following the opt-out procedure. 

## Use of Information.

We use your personally identifiable information: (a) to send you information regarding HasOffers and your Subscription to the Services; (b) to track your compliance with the HasOffers Services Agreement (“Services Agreement”); and/or (c) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Services and request for information regarding additional HasOffers products and/or services. 

## Information Sharing.

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, HasOffers will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to or with others. Parents are able to consent to our use of their child’s Personal Information without having also to consent to our disclosure of their child’s Personal Information to third parties as we will not share any information collected about a child through our client’s services with third parties. Notwithstanding the foregoing, HasOffers may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for credit card processing, offering customer service, efficiency purposes in providing administrative or program management services in connection with your Subscription to the Services such as billing and delivery. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by HasOffers. Further, HasOffers reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information: (a) where required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; (b) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of HasOffers’ business, assets or stock, in which case you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information; (c) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, and/or Services Agreement; (d) in the case of a dispute; or (e) where HasOffers determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of HasOffers and/or a third party, or necessary to protect HasOffers from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

## International Transfer of Data.

In the process of providing the Services to you, we may transfer information that we collect about you and your Subscription Users and any end users, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you or your End Users are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information and permitting the transfer of information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction. You consent to the transfer of your information to the United States and the use and disclosure of information about you and your Subscription Users and any end users, including personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## The HasOffers Blog.

The HasOffers blog, located at <http://www.hasoffers.com/blog/> is an optional resource for information and opinions related to the performance marketing industry. When you subscribe to the HasOffers blog, we will require you to provide us with your name and email address. By subscribing to the HasOffers blog you are agreeing to accept emails that include a compilation of blog posts and information about the HasOffers product line. You may opt-out of receiving such emails at any time by clicking on the link at the bottom of the emails or by emailing optout@hasoffers.com. The HasOffers blog is primarily designed to help you obtain and share information and opinions related to the performance marketing industry. Anytime you post on our blog please be aware that you are posting using a third party application and we have no access or control over this information. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, you can either log into the third party application and remove your comment or you can contact the appropriate third party application. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Data Retention.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@hasoffers.com](mailto:support@hasoffers.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Third Party Links.

The Site may contain links to third-party websites (“Third Party Websites”). Please be aware that HasOffers is not responsible for the privacy practices of Third Party Websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site. 

## Minors.

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. HasOffers will never knowingly collect any personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If HasOffers obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. If we engage in a contract with a client who we know wishes to collect information from users under the age of 13, we will ensure that our client represents and warrants that their collection practices comply with all legal requirements. **Pursuant to our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, our Customers may not use any HasOffers Service in a manner that does not comply with federal, state, or international law, including but not limited to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.** For the purposes of this provision, the definitions of “personal information” and “children” (and their translational and linguistic equivalents) are defined by the jurisdiction where the Customer is operating. In the United States, federal regulations related to the collection of personal information from children are codified at 15 U.S.C. 6501, et seq. 

## Your Employees.

Your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, in their entirety, shall inure to your employees, if any. You agree that any employee who accesses your Account, or who visits the Site under the scope of such employee’s employment with you (and any third party to whom you give rightful access to your Account or Site) agrees to the terms of this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, our use of cookies and/or web beacons. 

## Security.

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users’ information. When users submit personally identifiable information at the Site, their personally identifiable information is protected both online and offline. When our registration process asks users to submit Sensitive Information (such as bank account information), and when we transmit such Sensitive Information, that Sensitive Information is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we protect all other user information online and offline. The servers that we store personally identifiable information in are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information under our control. Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your personally identifiable information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees, and third party agents, that need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personally identifiable information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures. You acknowledge that you provide your personally identifiable information to HasOffers with knowledgeable consent and at your own risk. 

## Deleting and Updating Your Information.

If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you, simply send your request via certified mail to: HasOffers, Inc., 2220 Western Avenue, Seattle, WA 98121. You may also send your request via e-mail to: [support@hasoffers.com](mailto:support@hasoffers.com). We will respond to your access request within 30 days. We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Opting Out of Receiving E-mail.

You may at any time choose to stop receiving emails containing general information regarding HasOffers and/or HasOffers by following the instructions at the end of each such email or by contacting us at optout@hasoffers.com. There may be a short delay of up to several business days while your request is being verified, deployed and processed across our servers. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your Subscription to the Services, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. **Information Related to Data Collected through the HasOffers Platform** HasOffers collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. **Choice** We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. **Service Provider, Sub-Processors/Onward Transfer** HasOffers may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. **Access to Data Controlled by our Clients** HasOffers has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to HasOffers Client (the data controller). If the Client requests HasOffers to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days. **Data Retention** HasOffers will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. HasOffers will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Notification of Changes.

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we make material changes to how we use Personal Information collected from children under age 13, we will ensure that our Client notifies parents in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of the child’s Personal Information. 

## Safe Harbor.

HasOffers complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. HasOffers has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view HasOffers’ certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

## Contact Us.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: [privacy@hasoffers.com](mailto:privacy@hasoffers.com). HasOffers, Inc. 2220 Western Ave. Seattle WA, 98121 

## Exhibit A

## More about cookies on HasOffers.com

Using hasoffers.com requires the use of cookies. If you have do not want to accept the cookies for hasoffers.com or from any of our third parties, you won’t be able to use our service. We use a cookie to remember your cookie preferences this has a couple of consequences 

  * If you delete all your cookies you will have to update your preferences with us again.
  * If you use a different device, computer profile or browser you will have to tell us your preferences again.

The cookies used on hasoffers.com are based on the International Chamber of Commerce guide for cookie categories: 

  * Strictly necessary
  * Performance
  * Functionality

For more information about cookies see the further reading link below. 

## Strictly Necessary

‘Strictly Necessary’ cookies let you move around the website and login to your secure account. **These cookies don’t gather any information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you’ve been on the internet.** **We use these Strictly Necessary cookies to…**

  * Identify you as being logged in to hasoffers.com
  * Remember things like information you’ve entered on forms when you navigate to different pages in a single web browser session
  * Help you use specific features like testing tracking links
  * Make sure you connect to the right service on our website when we make any changes to the way the website works

**Cookies we have defined as ‘Strictly Necessary’ cookies will NOT be used to…**

  * Gather information that could be used to advertise products or services to you
  * Remember your preferences or username beyond your current visit

**Accepting these cookies is a condition of using the website, so if you prevent these cookies we can’t guarantee your security or predict how our website will perform during your visit.** **Here is a list of the cookies we have defined as ‘strictly necessary’.** **hasoffers.com cookies**

  * PHPSESSID

**Cookies provided by 3rd parties**

Cookie | Host  
---|---  
|   
|   
  
## Performance

‘Performance’ cookies collect information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience any errors. These cookies don’t collect any information that could identify you – all the information collected is anonymous and is only used to help us improve how our website works, understand what interests our users and measure how effective our advertising is. **We use performance cookies to…**

  * Provide statistics on how our website is used
  * See how effective our adverts are (we don’t use this information to target adverts to you when you visit other websites)
  * Provide feedback to partners that one of our visitors also visited their website. This can include details of any products bought. This lets our partners improve their website, but we don’t allow our partners to reuse this information for further advertising
  * Help us improve the website by measuring any errors that occur
  * Test different designs of our website

**Cookies we have defined as ‘Performance’ cookies will NOT be used to…**

  * Remember your preferences or username beyond your current visit

In some cases, some of these cookies are managed for us by third parties, but we don’t allow the third party to use the cookies for any purpose other than those listed above. **Using our site indicates that you accept the use of ‘Performance’ cookies.** **Accepting these cookies is a condition of using the website, so if you prevent them we cannot guarantee how our site will perform for you.** **Here is a list of the cookies we have defined as ‘Performance’.** **hasoffers.com cookies**

  * aff_conversions
  * __utma
  * __utmb
  * __utmc
  * __utmz
  * _pmy_visit
  * _pmy_visitor
  * is_returning
  * chartbeat2

**Cookies provided by 3rd parties**

Cookie | Host  
---|---  
|   
|   
  
## Functionality

‘Functionality’ cookies are used to provide services or to remember settings to improve your visit. **We use ‘Functionality’ cookies to…**

  * Remember settings you’ve applied such as layout, text size, preferences and colours
  * Remember if we’ve already asked you if you want to fill in a survey
  * Provide proactive live chat sessions to offer you support or submit a trouble ticket
  * Show you when you’re logged in to the website
  * Share information with partners to provide a service on our website. The information shared is only to be used to provide the service, product or function and not for any other purpose

**Cookies defined as ‘Functionality’ will not be used to…**

  * Target you with adverts on other websites

Some of these cookies are managed for us by third parties – where this is the case we don’t allow the third party to use the cookies for any purpose other than those listed above. **You can control whether or not these cookies are used, but preventing them may mean we can’t offer you some services, and will reduce the support we can offer you.** It’s also possible that preventing these cookie stops us remembering that you didn’t want a specific service. **Here is a list of the cookies we have defined as ‘Functionality’.** **hasoffers.com cookies**

  * app_user
  * swidth

**Cookies provided by 3rd parties**

Cookie | Host  
---|---  
edition | .hasoffers.com  
network_id | .hasoffers.com  
networkname | .hasoffers.com  
networkurl | .hasoffers.com  
__lc.serverchat1c | .livechatinc.com  
redirect | .adroll.com  
  
## Further reading

**Information about cookies**

Useful information about cookies can be found at:

**Internet Advertising Bureau**

A guide to behavioural advertising and online privacy has been produced by the internet advertising industry which can be found at:

**International Chamber of Commerce United Kingdom**

Information on the ICC (UK) UK cookie guide can be found on the ICC website section:

<http://www.international-chamber.co.uk/our-expertise/digitaleconomy>
